Register to the Papers of Vladimir and Wanda Toscanini Horowitz
Yale University Music Library
- MISCELLANEOUS ITEMS, 1866-1991; Series IX; 27 boxes (11.25')
  - Items Pertaining to Vladimir Horowitz, Wanda Toscanini Horowitz, and Sonia Horowitz, IX.A
    - Books and pamphlets
      - Carnegie Hall: Looking Ahead., n.d.; 1 item. (Box 121, Folder 29)
        A.l.: s.n., n.d.
        [20] p.; 28cm.
      - Cento di Concerti della Societa' Del Quartetto di Milano. -- Milan, 1964, 1 item. (Box 121)
        [368] p.; 33 cm.
        Preface by Giulio Confalonieri
        Separate booklet with English translation of preface (xliii p.) laid in
      - Motsart: Issledovatel'skii etiud, n.d.; Chicherin, G.; 1 item. (Box 121, Folder 30)
        [319] p. [i.e. 158 sheets]; 16 x 23 cm.
      - On the proper performance of all Beethoven's works for the piano / Edited and with a Commentary by Paul Badura-Skoda. Wien: Universal Edition, 1970., Czerny, Carl, 1791-1857; 1 item. (Box 121)
        12, 119 p.; 30 cm.
      - Systematic introduction to improvisation on the pianoforte / Translated and Edited by Alice L. Mitchell. New York: Longman, 1983., Czerny, Carl, 1791-1857; 1 item. (Box 121)
        xiv, 129 p.; 25 cm.
      - Performance guide in the study of Clementi's Sonatas: a thesis submitted in partial fulfilment of the requirements for the degree Doctor of Musical Arts at the University Wisconsin, 1977, Di Piazza, Joseph Anthony; 1 item. (Box 122)
        2, 111 p., bound; 29 cm.
        Autograph letter signed (photocopy) from author to Vladimir Horowitz and photo laid in
      - Indigenous Patterns and the Hotel Okura., 1982 May; 1 item. (Box 122)
        Tokyo: Iwajiro Noda, May 1982 (Revised edition)
        194 p.; 31 cm.
        Inscription on title page from the Honorable Chairman, Tokyo, 1983 June 15
        Brochure laid in
      - Köchel, Dr. Ludwig Ritter von Koechel ABC / Edited by Hellmuth von Hase; English adaptation of the introduction by Robert Sabin. Wiesbaden: Breitkopf & Härtel, 1965., 1 item. (Box 122)
        97 p.; 21 cm.
        Fifth edition
      - Milano Bella: nella sue stampe / Giorgio Lise e Claudio Salsi Comune di Milano, 1985, Lise, Giorgio; 1 item. (Box 154)
        [50] p.; 31 x 40 cm.
        Inscription on front fly leaf from Paolo Pillitteri [note laid in: Mayor of Milan 1987? 1986?]
      - Puccini: a biography / by George R. Marek New York: Simon and Schuster, 1951, Marek, George R.; 1 item. (Box 122, Folder 31)
        Photocopy of pp. 262-265
      - The letters of Wolfgang Amadeus Mozart (1769-1791) / Translated from the collection of Ludwig Nohl, by Lady Wallace New York: Hurd and Houghton; Philadelphia: Frederick Leypoldt, 1866., Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791; 1 item. (Box 122)
        xv, 332 p.; 18 cm. Vol. I Bound with: Vol. II (vii, 297 p.)
        Pages marked by Vladimir Horowitz Leaf (pp. 71-72) from book, Letters of Composers, laid in
      - 1968 Annual Report to the Shareholders of Columbia Broadcasting System, Inc. for the year ended December 28, 1968. S.l.: s.n., n.d., 1 item. (Box 122, Folder 31)
        63 p.; 26 cm.
      - Quellen Russischer Weisheit. St. Gallen: Leobuchhandlung, n.d., 1 item. (Box 122, Folder 31)
        21 p.; 13 cm.
      - 16 Afbeeldingen Naar Staalgravures uit 1850 van Stad Amsterdam. S.l.: Van Beroemde Tekenaarsen Graveurs, n.d., 1 item. (Box 123, Folder 32)
        [16] leaves; 30 cm.
      - University Musical Society of University of Michigan celebrates 100 years 1879-1979 / [edited by] Barbara Ferguson. [Ann Arbor]: The University Musical Society of the University of Michigan, 1980., 1 item. (Box 123, Folder 32)
        207 p.; 28 cm.
        Typed letter signed (copy) from Gail Rector to Vladimir Horowitz laid in
      - Stat'i materialy, vospominaniia Moscow: Sovetskii Kompozitor, 1980., Zak, Iakov; 1 item. (Box 123)
        [208] p.; 22 cm.
        Inscription on front fly leaf: Prof. M. Sokolov, 25 April 1986
      - Page cut from unidentified book, n.d.; 1 item. (Box 123, Folder 32)
        Note by Suzanne Fusso: "Page from a book showing photo of Vladimir Horowitz and the dedication on the back to Boris Vladimirovich Asaf'ev-Glebov, in memory of their meeting in St. Petersburg in Nov. 1923. Dated 22 Nov. 1923"
    - Portraits and caricatures of or having to do with Vladimir Horowitz
      - n.d., Bendiner, Alfred; 3 items. (Box 123, Folder 33)
        19 x 16 cm.
        Pen and ink with inscription
        Includes 2 copies without inscription, 21 x 21 cm., and 24 x 36 cm.
      - n.d., Hine, J. (Folder Oversized Folder (ovf))
        62 x 50 cm.
        Pen and ink
      - n.d., 1 item. (Box 123, Folder 33)
        28 cm.
        Charcoal? (copy of a page from a book?)
        Creator unknown, possibly Lupas (firstname unknown).
      - 1946, Mévi, J.; 1 item. (Box 123, Folder 33)
        Negative etching? (portrait of Vladimir Horowitz scratched off of black layer of paint to reveal white layer underneath)
      - n.d., Mitchell, Joan Cameron; 1 item. (Box 154)
        48 x 39 cm.
        Charcoal
      - ca. 1978 Jan. 6, Roseman, S.; 1 item. (Box 154)
        49 cm.
        Framed pencil sketch
        In pencil in bottom left corner: Vladimir Horowitz "Rachmaninoff Piano Concerto #3" rehearsal - 50th Anniversary performance Carnegie Hall - January 6, 1978 c S. Roseman
      - n.d., 1 item.
        94 x 79 cm.
        Framed pen and ink/watercolor
        Plaque on frame reads: Presented with the Compliments of Reader's Digest
        Creator unknown, possibly Sokoloff (firstname unknown).
      - 1943, 1 item. (Box 123, Folder 34)
        29 x 23 cm.
        Framed charcoal
        Creator unknown, possibly Eugen Spiro.
      - 1947 Dec. 3, Warner, H.; 1 item. (Box 123, Folder 33)
        23 x 23 cm.
        Inscription: From The Arizona Times, Phoenix, Arizona...
      - 1980, Unidentified; 2 items. (Box 123, Folder 33)
        Two printed copies of a sketch of Vladimir Horowitz
      - n.d., Unidentified; 1 item. (Box 123, Folder 33)
        14 x 9 cm.
        Pencil sketch of Vladimir Horowitz
      - Unidentified comic strip with Vladimir Horowitz as the subject, n.d.; 1 item. (Box 123, Folder 33)
        2 sheets; 25 x 29 cm.
        Pen and ink with blue pencil markings "Washington Post Syndicate, Inc." pasted on
    - Ticket stubs, 1928-1988; 14 items. (Box 124, Folder 35)
      In part, copies
    - Advertisements
      - Brochures and fliers, 1926-1992; 77 items. (Box 124, Folder 36-42)
      - Magazine/newspaper proof sheets, 1965-1989; 23 items. (Box 154/161)
        Autograph letter signed from Diane Gould (1978 Jan. 13) laid in with Newsweek proof
      - Record album proofsheets, ca. 1991; 8 items. (Box 124/154)
        Typed letter signed(copy) from Peter Gelb laid in
      - Proofsheets for analytical notes for video, Horowitz, the Story-Teller, 1990; 1 item. (Box 124, Folder 42)
      - Posters and displays, 1926-1989; 49 items. (Box 155-161 and 2 oversize posters)
    - Calendars, 1987-1989; 6 items. (Box 161)
    - Portraits of musicians, etc.
      - Brahms, Johannes, n.d.; 1 item. (Box 162)
        Framed silhouette
      - Chopin, Frederic, n.d.; 1 item. (Box 162)
        Framed plaster relief of bust
      - 2 prints and a postcard, 3 items. (Box 162)
      - Liszt, Franz, n.d.; 1 item. (Box 162)
        Plaster cast of bust
        Card laid in with inscription from Edwin Bachman, N.Y., 1941 Mar. 25
      - Framed print signed by artist, Bauer?, n.d.; 1 item. (Box 162)
      - Postcards, n.d.; 2 items. (Box 162)
      - Schumann, Robert, n.d.; 1 item. (Box 162)
        Framed print
        Inscription on back - gift of Elmar Weingarten and Angela [Zwick?], Berlin, 1986 May 27
      - Tolstoi, Leo, n.d.; 1 item. (Box 162)
        Print
    - Miscellaneous items
      - Bill for Franz Liszt from Friedrich Rinck of the Gasthaus "Zum weissen Ross" - front and back contain pencil notes - sheet of paper with more notes laid in, 1956 Aug. 3; 2 items. (Box 124, Folder 43)
      - 500 rubles bill, U.S.S.R., 1912; 1 item. (Box 124, Folder 43)
      - Silver cigarette case, wedding gift from Wanda Toscanini Horowitz to Vladimir Horowitz, ca. 1933 Dec. 21; 1 item. (Box 126)
      - Wallet, birthday gift of Rudi and Irene Serkin, card laid in, 1938 Oct. 1; 1 item. (Box 126)
      - Brochure and flier for the George Junior Republic school which Sonia Horowitz attended, ca. 1948; 2 items. (Box 124, Folder 44)
      - $2.00 bills, U.S.A., 1953-1976; 2 items. (Box 124, Folder 44)
      - Advertisement for a show of the paintings of Boris Chaliapin, 1959 Mar.-Apr.; 2 items. (Box 124, Folder 44)
      - Laminated article from the New York Times, 1965 April 27, ca. 1965 Apr. 27; 1 item. (Box 124, Folder 44)
      - Items pertaining to the Vladimir Horowitz fan party for some of those who waited in the ticket line, 1966-1967; 28 items. (Box 124, Folder 44)
      - Ticket line list, 1968 Nov. 24; 1 item. (Box 160)
      - Ticket line list, 1968 Dec. 15; 1 item. (Box 124, Folder 45)
      - Baseballs signed by members of the N.Y. Mets and St. Louis Cardinals teams at Shea Stadium, 1969 June 20; 2 items. (Box 125)
      - RCA envelope with "Vladimir Horowitz is a National Treasure" stamp, 1970 June 15; 2 items. (Box 124, Folder 45)
      - Chart with the flags of the U.S., 1973; 4 items. (Box 124, Folder 46)
      - Certificates in memory of Sonia Horowitz, 1976 Nov.-Dec.; 2 items. (Box 124, Folder 47)
      - Commemorative silver chip for the opening of Casino Scheveningen, certificate laid in, 1979 Oct. 4; 1 item. (Box 127)
      - Stubs for Fortune Society drawing, ca. 1980 Oct. 30; 10 items. (Box 124, Folder 47)
      - Sign for Vladimir Horowitz's lost cat, Fussy, 1980; 1 item. (Box 124, Folder 48)
      - Cartier gold lighter, 1984 Oct. 1; 1 item. (Box 127)
        includes certificate of purchase
      - Arturo Toscanini bookends, 1985 May 1; 1 item. (Box 153)
        Franklin Mint, certificate, Typed letter signed, and brochure laid in
      - Vladimir Horowitz potholder, ca. 1985 Dec. 20?; 1 item. (Box 153)
      - Information for an Arizona/ Florida vacation, winter 1985, 5 items. (Box 124, Folder 49)
        Note on discarded envelope: never went
      - Silver calliope, found in box stamped: B.V. Juweliersbedrijf Herman Schipper Diamonds... Amsterdam, 1986; 1 item. (Box 126)
      - Framed L. Ron Hubbard quote, 1987 June 30; 1 item. (Box 163)
        gift of fan whose Typed letter signed (copy) is laid in
      - Small wallet with Vladimir Horowitz's Holland Casinos card (1987) inside, 1 item. (Box 126)
      - Lucite paperweight, compliments of Deutsche Grammophon, ca. 1987; 1 item. (Box 127)
        Note from Allison Ames laid in
      - Silver photograph frame, gift of Mdm. Wally Toscanini to Vladimir Horowitz on the occasion of his 50th anniversary concert, ca. 1989 Jan. 8; 1 item. (Box 127)
      - Swatch watch, 1989; 1 item. (Box 127)
      - Leather wallets, 3 items. (Box 126)
      - Floor pattern of Steinway Grand Model D, 1 item. (Box 124, Folder 50)
      - Questionnaire concerning ticket distribution for ticket-holders of a Vladimir Horowitz concert, n.d.; 1 item. (Box 124, Folder 51)
      - Japanese watercolor in folder, n.d.; 1 item. (Box 124, Folder 52)
      - Joseph Schillinger information, n.d.; 1 item. (Box 124, Folder 53)
      - Sticker reading "Fly Horowitz", n.d.; 5 items. (Box 124, Folder 54)
      - Matchbook covers advertising Tschaikowsky Concerto No. 1 in B Flat Minor Horowitz Toscanini and the NBC Symphony Orchestra Victor Records, 2 items. (Box 124, Folder 54)
      - Business cards for David Rubin, Christel Michalke, Thomas Frost Productions, Wladimir I. Iwanow, and Edward P. Djerejian, 5 items. (Box 124, Folder 54)
      - Sheet with notes by Wanda Toscanini Horowitz? and another, 1 item. (Box 124, Folder 54)
      - Page 4 of a tribute to Vladimir Horowitz, n.d.; 1 item. (Box 124, Folder 54)
      - Brochure for the photographer, R.T. Kahn, n.d.; 1 item. (Box 124, Folder 54)
      - Presidential seal cuff links and pin, gift of President Ronald Reagan, 3 items. (Box 127)
      - Paperweights? -brass and chrome initials "V" and "H", 2 items. (Box 127)
      - Cardboard music box made by Japanese fan for Christmas, n.d.; 1 item. (Box 153)
      - Yale University, Silliman College, pewter mug, n.d.; 1 item. (Box 153)
      - Silk flower bouquet with card laid in: "I love Horowitz Kyoko", n.d.; 1 item. (Box 153)
      - Small Steinway & Sons sculpture fashioned from piano parts, n.d.; 1 item. (Box 153)
      - Piano pencil sharpener, n.d.; 1 item. (Box 153)
      - Vladimir Horowitz's stamp with Carnegie Hall address, n.d.; 1 item. (Box 126)
      - Gold money clip, gift of Jascha Heifetz, n.d.; 1 item. (Box 126)
      - Silver cigarette holder made in Russia, "gift to Vladimir Horowitz from his brother Jacob", n.d.; 1 item. (Box 126)
        [note on discarded box]
      - Copper block plate of Vladimir Horowitz in Russia, n.d.; 1 item. (Box 126)
      - Silver folding frame gift from Wanda Toscanini Horowitz to Vladimir Horowitz, originally held 2 photographs of Sonia, 1 item. (Box 126)
        See: PHOTOGRAPHS
      - Copper engraving plate, "Vladimir and Wanda Horowitz", 1 item. (Box 126)
      - Framed program cover? - "Horowitz-Live!", n.d.; 1 item. (Box 160)
      - Framed copy of review of Vladimir Horowitz's U.S. debut, New York Times, 13 January 1928, n.d.; 1 item. (Box 163)
      - Prints of photographs of the Soviet Union by Michael Reagan, n.d.; 1 item. (Box 163)
      - Crystal cologne bottles with "V.H." engraved on silver caps, 2 items. (Box 153)
      - Penknife and bottle with ivory handles, 2 items. (Box 153)
        ("V.H." engraved on penknife)
      - Pin commemorating the 100th anniversary of the Moscow Conservatory, 1 item. (Box 153)
      - Baume & Mercier platinum, very thin pocket watch, ca. 1925; 1 item. (Box 128)
        The sides and top of the watch are set with diamonds. A 14k white gold watch chain with 3 natural 2mm pearls is attached
      - Cartier cigarette case 18k yellow and pink gold with black enamel sides, ca. 1935; 1 item. (Box 128)
      - Cartier cufflinks, ca. 1935; 1 item. (Box 128)
        The platinum cufflinks consist of a bar set with a cabochon sapphire on each end and 2 circles with diamonds set on one side and square cut sapphires set on the other
      - Rolex man's wrist watch 18k gold oyster marked Tiffany & Co. on the dial. The back of the watch is inscribed: "Vladimir Horowitz from NYP [New York Philharmonic] Jan 12 1928-1978, ca. 1978; 1 item. (Box 128)
      - Van Cleef & Arpels cigarette case, n.d.; 1 item. (Box 128)
        18k yellow gold with two rows of square cut sapphires set down the top. Each row contains 22 sapphires
      - Medallion of St. Francis of Assisi, n.d.; 1 item. (Box 128)
        Oval bas-relief ivory carving, 1 5/8 x 2 1/4", within a rectangular dark brown walnut frame (lacquered) 3 1/2 x 2 7/8", on the verso of which is its handwritten provenance (see below), preserved in a later red morocco gilt-stamped Santos de Cartier jewelry box 4 11/16 x 4 1/6", light scratches to the frame with small losses of the lacquered surface in two places, a white glue appearing substance has leaked out from behind the carving.
        Provenance: gift of Daniele, the daughter of Hans von Bülow (1830-1894) and Cosima (Liszt's daughter) to Franz Liszt, who, tradition holds, kept it on his night-stand, subsequently giving it to Professor Wilhelm Guida. From Professor Guida the medallion passed to Friedelind Wagner (daughter of Richard Wagner's son, Siegfried). She gave it to Arturo Toscanini (he helped Friedelind immigrate to America), and Toscanini gave the carving to his son- in-law, Vladimir Horowitz, who kept it on his night-stand like his great hero, Franz Liszt [by Kenneth Nesheim]
      - 35 metal printing plates with portraits of Vladimir Horowitz, some mounted on wooden blocks, and 33 proof-sheets, 68 items. (Box 129)
      - Concert dress and other clothing belonging to Vladimir Horowitz:, 8 items. (Box 164)
        2 bowties
        suspenders
        monogrammed silk scarf
        jacket
        pants
        2 vests
        pair of leather gloves
        pair of leather gloves (Truzzi)
  - Items pertaining to Arturo Toscanini, IX.B
    - Program for Arturo Toscanini performance of Falstaff at La Scala, 1921-1922; 1 item. (Box 130, Folder 55)
    - Will belonging to Arturo Toscanini and in his hand (photocopy), 1930 June 23; 1 item. (Box 130, Folder 55)
    - NBC brochure advertising Toscanini broadcasts, 1938; 1 item. (Box 130, Folder 55)
    - Baton used by Arturo Toscanini to conduct the Brahms B-flat major concerto with Vladimir Horowitz in Lucerne, 1939 Aug.; 1 item. (Box 207)
    - Advertisement for concert with Arturo Toscanini and the Los Angeles Philharmonic, ca. 1945 Mar. 2; 1 item. (Box 130, Folder 55)
    - Items pertaining to Arturo Toscanini's death
      - Typescript from "Edward P. Morgan and the News," 1957 Jan. 16, ABC, ca. 1957 Jan. 16; 1 item. (Box 130, Folder 56)
      - Ticket for services for Arturo Toscanini at St. Patrick's Cathedral, 1957 Jan. 19; 1 item. (Box 130, Folder 56)
      - Condolences sent to Wanda Toscanini Horowitz, 1957-1858; 15 items. (Box 130, Folder 56)
        (photocopies, originals with I. CORRESPONDENCE)
      - Draft of letter from Wanda Toscanini Horowitz to President Eisenhower, ca. 1957 Jan.; 1 item. (Box 130, Folder 56)
      - Radio script (typescript) - Mrs. Belmont eulogizing Arturo Toscanini, ca. 1957 Jan.; 1 item. (Box 130, Folder 56)
      - "In Memoriam Arturo Toscanini" - flier from the Philharmonic Symphony Orchestra, ca. 1957 Jan. 20; 1 item. (Box 130, Folder 56)
      - Programs for Arturo Toscanini memorial concerts, 1957 Jan.-Feb.; 3 items. (Box 130, Folder 56)
      - Program for requiem mass for Arturo Toscanini at St. James's Church, London, 1957 Jan. 16; 1 item. (Box 130, Folder 56)
      - Items pertaining to events honoring Arturo Toscanini in Parma, 1958-1959; 6 items. (Box 130, Folder 56)
      - America-Italy Newsletter, with announcement of program commemorating Arturo Toscanini, 1959 Jan. 15, 1958 Dec.; 1 item. (Box 130, Folder 56)
    - Arturo Toscanini: A Complete Discography. S.l.: Radio Corporation of America, RCA Victor Record Division, May 1965, 1 item. (Box 130, Folder 57)
      [38] p.; 25 cm.
      Includes pencil and ink additions
    - Arturo Toscanini: A Complete Discography. S.l.: Radio Corporation of America, RCA Victor Record Division, October 1966, 1 item. (Box 130, Folder 57)
      [62] p.; 25 cm.
    - Toscanini first day of issue envelopes and stamps, Italy, 1967 Mar.; 9 items. (Box 130, Folder 57)
    - Maggio Musicale Fiorentino celebrating the 100th anniversary of Arturo Toscanini's birth, 1967 May; 1 item. (Box 130, Folder 57)
    - Solenidade de entriga ao Teatro de uma escultura em bronze do imortal Maestro Arturo Toscanini no ano do centenário co seu nascimento, Rio de Janeiro, 1967 Nov. 10; 1 item. (Box 130, Folder 57)
      Typed letter signed from Victor Civita to Wanda Toscanini Horowitz, 1967 Nov. 28 laid in
    - Poster for Arturo Toscanini recording, Seraphim IC-6015, Beethoven Symphonies Nos. 1, 4, & 6, 1967; 1 item. (Box 130, Folder 57)
    - Microfilm of Toscanini collection at the New York Public Library, ca. 1969; 1 item. (Box 130)
      in microfilm box postmarked 1969 Jan. 28
    - Entertainment Hall of Fame Foundation certificate of nomination and Typed letter signed laid in, 1976; 2 items. (Box 130, Folder 57)
    - National Public Radio folder for "Toscanini -- the Man Behind the Legend", 1978; 5 items. (Box 130, Folder 58)
      includes press release, schedule, photos - 5 copies
    - Inventory of the music of Arturo Toscanini, in Milan, now at the New York Public Library, 1982; 2 items. (Box 130, Folder 59)
    - Franklin Mint Almanac, March/ April 1983, Vol. 14, No. 2, 2 items. (Box 130, Folder 60)
      contains articles about Toscanini and advertisement for Toscanini bookends
    - Toscanini / by John W. Freeman and Walfredo Toscanini. New York: Treves Publishing Company, 1987, 1 item. (Box 130, Folder 61)
      75 p.; 29 cm.
    - Items pertaining to the Arturo Toscanini Commemorative U.S. Postage Stamp March 25, 1989, 37 items. (Box 130, 160, Folder 62)
      Includes stamps, presentation book for Wanda Toscanini Horowitz, 2 cards containing notes for remarks by Wanda Toscanini Horowitz, poster, correspondence (Wanda Toscanini Horowitz and U.S. Postal Service, Walfredo Toscanini, and Peter Gelb), an agreement, receipts for certified mail, first day of issue envelopes for Toscanini and Liszt, program, and an honorary certificate from Mario Cuomo and the State of New York - includes italian stamps commemorating Toscanini
    - Casa Toscanini: a short guide to the Museum. Parma: Grafiche Step, 1990, 1 item. (Box 130, Folder 63)
      36 p.; 24 cm.
      Inscribed by Wally Toscanini Castelbarco on front fly leaf, 1991 May 18
    - Spiral-bound book of photocopies of clippings for "Bologna per Toscanini," 1991 May 14-15, 1 item. (Box 130, Folder 63)
    - Jottings in Arturo Toscanini's hand, 6 items. (Box 131, Folder 64)
      [6] sheets; 10-19 cm.
      Holographs in pencil
    - Portrait (print) of Toscanini, signed by artist, n.d.; 1 item. (Box 131, Folder 64)
    - Photographs of scenes in Toscanini Casa Natale, in Parma, on post cards, n.d.; 9 items. (Box 131, Folder 65)
    - Bookplate for the Brandeis University Library in memorium Arturo Toscanini given by Dr. and Mrs. Leopold U. Sherry, 2 items. (Box 131, Folder 65)
    - [18] p. from an unidentified book or pamphlet about Arturo Toscanini, n.d.; 1 item. (Box 131, Folder 65)
    - The Toscanini Legacy, catalog of items at the New York Public Library, n.d.; 1 item. (Box 131, Folder 66-67)
    - Photographs of a Swiss sculpture and monument to Arturo Toscanini, 2 items. (Box 131, Folder 68)